{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","address":"100 Renaissance Cen Ste. 2102","zipcode":"48243","owner":"Tony Curtis - Papa Joe's Gourm","licenseNumber":"221010","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/19/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E610000088E8BD828BC254C04809E8951D2A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43801","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","inspectionDate":"2018-10-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43801","inspectionDate":"10/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER BUCKETS","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"43801","inspectionDate":"10/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"40464","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","inspectionDate":"2017-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40464","inspectionDate":"10/10/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"40464","inspectionDate":"10/10/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\r\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Food","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate to a designated area that does not contaminate items or surfaces."},{"inspectionid":"40464","inspectionDate":"10/10/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Damaged","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"39989","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","inspectionDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inspectorid":"80","pcount":"3","pfcount":"6","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"9","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"9","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"ENTIRE FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"4-603.14","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be effectively washed to remove or completely loosen soils by using the manual or mechanical means necessary such as the application of detergents containing wetting agents and emulsifiers; acid, alkaline, or abrasive cleaners; hot water; brushes; scouring pads; high-pressure sprays; or ultrasonic devices.\r\n(B) The washing procedures selected shall be based on the type and purpose of the EQUIPMENT or UTENSIL, and on the type of soil to be removed.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Washing agent(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not utilized","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize cleaning agents as specified above."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ENTIRE FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not repaired according to law","subProblem":"","location":"ENTIRE FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Prep sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair according to law."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient water source/system to meet demand."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide additional equipment to meet requirement above."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between drain line and flood rim of receiving drain","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"5-204.12","violationDescription":"A backflow prevention device shall be located so that it may be serviced and maintained.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Backflow prevention device(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not conveniently located","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Coffee machines","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make convenient by relocating."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ENTIRE FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide additional equipment to meet requirement above."},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"39989","inspectionDate":"9/19/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622523","name":"Starbucks - Renaissance Center","violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622523"}}